braou.ac.in 2018-03-28

# Privacy-Policy – BRAOU

Privacy Statement

Your privacy is important to us.

It is Dr.B.R.Ambedkar Open University policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while you are operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy so as to make you understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of your personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.

  * We shall collect personal information by lawful & fair means and wherever appropriate with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is beingcollected.
  * We shall collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to- date.
  * We shall protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We shall make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
  * We shall only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Dr.B.R.Ambedkar Open University may change this privacy policy from time to time at Dr.B.R.Ambedkar Open University sole discretion.
